Guide to the Time Inc. Subject Files 1889-2015 (bulk 1934-1993) MS 3009-RG 1
New-York Historical Society
- Series II: 1961 and Later, 1936-2015; 196504; 50 Linear feet (50 boxes)
  - Time-Life Broadcast: Miscellaneous: 1969, 196645 (Offsite-box 493, Folder 3-4)
  - Time-Life Broadcast: Miscellaneous: 1970-1972, 196644 (Offsite-box 493)
  - Time-Life Broadcast: Miscellaneous: 1970-1972 [RESTRICTED], 196643 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Broadcast: Programming: 1969 & Before, 196642 (Offsite-box 493, Folder 7-8)
  - Time-Life Broadcast: International: 1971 & Before, 196641 (Offsite-box 493, Folder 9)
  - Time-Life Broadcast: International: 1961-1970, 196640 (Offsite-box 493)
  - Time-Life Broadcast: International: 1961-1970 [RESTRICTED], 196639 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Cable Communications: 1972 & Later, 196638 (Offsite-box 493)
  - Time-Life Cable Communications: 1972 & Later [RESTRICTED], 196637 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life (Corporate): 1992- [empty], 196636 (Offsite-box 493, Folder 14)
  - Time-Life Films: 1969, 196635 (Offsite-box 493)
  - Time-Life Films: 1969 [RESTRICTED], 196634 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1970: Miscellaneous, 196633 (Offsite-box 493, Folder 16)
  - Time-Life Films: 1970: BBC/T-L Film Agreement, 196632 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1971: BBC, 196631 (Offsite-box 493, Folder 17)
  - Time-Life Films: 1971: Miscellaneous, 196630 (Offsite-box 493, Folder 18)
  - Time-Life Films: 1972: America Book Deal, 196629 (Offsite-box 493)
  - Time-Life Films: 1972: America Book Deal [RESTRICTED], 196628 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1972: BBC, 196627 (Offsite-box 493, Folder 20)
  - Time-Life Films: 1972: Miscellaneous, 196626 (Offsite-box 493, Folder 21)
  - Time-Life Films: 1973: BBC, 196625 (Offsite-box 493)
  - Time-Life Films: 1973: BBC [RESTRICTED], 196624 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1973: Miscellaneous, 196623 (Offsite-box 493-494)
  - Time-Life Films: 1973: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 196622 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1974: BBC, 196621 (Offsite-box 494)
  - Time-Life Films: 1974: BBC [RESTRICTED], 196620 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1974: Miscellaneous, 196619 (Offsite-box 493)
  - Time-Life Films: 1974: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 196618 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1975: Miscellaneous: Jan.-June, 196617 (Offsite-box 494, Folder 4)
  - Time-Life Films: 1975: Miscellaneous: July-Dec., 196616 (Offsite-box 494, Folder 5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1975: BBC, 196615 (Offsite-box 494, Folder 6)
  - Time-Life Films: 1976: Miscellaneous, 196614 (Offsite-box 494)
  - Time-Life Films: 1976: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 196613 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1975-1978: T-L Television Books: Wild, Wild World of Animals, 196612 (Offsite-box 494, Folder 8)
  - Time-Life Films: 1977: BBC, 196611 (Offsite-box 494, Folder 9)
  - Time-Life Films: 1975-1979: T-L Television Books: Miscellaneous, 196610 (Offsite-box 494)
  - Time-Life Films: 1975-1979: T-L Television Books: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 196609 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1976: BBC, 196608 (Offsite-box 494)
  - Time-Life Films: 1976: BBC [RESTRICTED], 196607 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1977: Talent Associates Acquisition, 196606 (Offsite-box 494)
  - Time-Life Films: 1977: Talent Associates Acquisition [RESTRICTED], 196605 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1977: Miscellaneous, 196604 (Offsite-box 494)
  - Time-Life Films: 1977: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 196603 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1977: Shakespeare Plays: Book Project Attempt, 196602 (Offsite-box 494, Folder 15)
  - Time-Life Films: 1977: T-L Television Books: Life Goes to War, 196601 (Offsite-box 494, Folder 16)
  - Time-Life Films: 1978: BBC, 196600 (Offsite-box 494, Folder 17)
  - Time-Life Films: 1978: Miscellaneous, 196599 (Offsite-box 494)
  - Time-Life Films: 1978: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 196598 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1979: BBC, 196597 (Offsite-box 494, Folder 20)
  - Time-Life Films: 1979: Miscellaneous, 196596 (Offsite-box 494, Folder 21-22)
  - Time-Life Films: 1979-1980: Time-Life Satellite Network, 196595 (Offsite-box 494, Folder 23)
  - Time-Life Films: 1980 & Later, 196594 (Offsite-box 494, Folder 24)
  - Time-Life Films: 1978-1981: Time-Life Video Club, 196593 (Offsite-box 494)
  - Time-Life Films: 1978-1981: Time-Life Video Club [RESTRICTED], 196592 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Home Video, 196591 (Offsite-box 494, Folder 26)
  - Time Life Inc.: Formerly Time-Life Books Inc.: 1992-, 196590 (Offsite-box 494, Folder 27)
  - Time-Life Libraries, Inc., 196589 (Offsite-box 494, Folder 28)
  - Time-Life Records: 1961-1962, 196588 (Offsite-box 495)
  - Time-Life Records: 1961-1962 [RESTRICTED], 196587 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Records: 1963-1964, 196586 (Offsite-box 495)
  - Time-Life Records: 1963-1964 [RESTRICTED], 196585 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Video: 1971-1973: Speed Reading Course with Dick Cavett, 196584 (Offsite-box 495)
  - Time-Life Video: 1971-1973: Speed Reading Course with Dick Cavett [RESTRICTED], 196583 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Records: 1965, 196582 (Offsite-box 495)
  - Time-Life Records: 1965 [RESTRICTED], 196581 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Records: 1966, 196580 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 5)
  - Time-Life Records: 1967-1969, 196579 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 6)
  - Time-Life Records: 1970 & Later, 196578 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 7)
  - Time-Life Records: International, 196577 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 8)
  - Time Warner Trade Publishing: Miscellaneous, 196576 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 9)
  - Time-Life Video: 1972-1973: T-L Video Center, 196575 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 10)
  - Time-Life Video: 1970, 196574 (Offsite-box 495)
  - Time-Life Video: 1970 [RESTRICTED], 196573 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Video: 1971: Miscellaneous, 196572 (Offsite-box 495)
  - Time-Life Video: 1971: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 196571 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Video: 1972: Miscellaneous, 196570 (Offsite-box 495)
  - Time-Life Video: 1972: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 196569 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Video: 1973-Spring 1991, 196568 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 17)
  - Time-Life Video & Television (TLVT): 1991 & Later, 196567 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 18)
  - Time Warner Books, 196566 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 19)
  - Time Warner Cable Group: 1989-1991, 196565 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 20)
  - Time Warner Cable Group: 1992-, 196564 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 21)
  - Time Warner Cable Group: New York 1 News: 24 Hour News Channel, 196563 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 22)
  - Time Warner Entertainment, 196562 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 23-24)
  - Time Warner Enterprises: Court TV, 196561 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 25)
  - Time Warner Enterprises: Six Flags Corporation, 196560 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 26)
  - Time Warner Enterprises: Miscellaneous, 196559 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 27)
  - Time Warner International Inc., 196558 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 28)
  - Time Warner Libraries, Inc., 196557 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 29)
  - Time Warner Publishing, Inc., 196556 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 30)
  - Time Warner Sports, 196555 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 31)
  - Time Warner Telecommunications Inc, 196554 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 32)
  - Time Warner Ventures, 196553 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 1)
  - Time World Newsradio Service, 196552 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 2)
  - Travel & Entertainment Accounting Department: 1987, 196551 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 3)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1965-1970, 196550 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 4)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1971-1980, 196549 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 5)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1975: Cost Control Committee, 196548 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 6)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1981 & Later, 196547 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 7)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1981: Pre-Publication, 196546 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 8)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1981: Pre-Publication Dummies, 196545 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 9)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1981: Pre-Publication, 196544 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 10)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1982: Pre-Publication, 196543 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 11)
  - TV-Cable Week: Pre-Publication, 196542 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 12-13)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1982: Pre-Publication: Prospectus, 196541 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 14)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1982: Pre-Publication: Dummy, 196540 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 15)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1982: Pre-Publication, 196539 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 16)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1983: Pre-Publication, 196538 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 17)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1983: First Issue, 196537 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 18)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1983: Last Issue, 196536 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 19)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1983: Pre-Publication, 196535 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 20)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1983: Publishing, 196534 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 22)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1984, 196533 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 23)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1983: Edit, 196532 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 24)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1983: Publishing, 196531 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 25)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1961-, 196530 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 26-27)
  - Turner Broadcasting System, Inc. (TBS), 196529 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 28)
  - Vibe, 196528 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 29)
  - Video Group: 1970-1975, 196527 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 30-31)
  - Video Group: 1976-2003, 196526 (Offsite-box 496-497)
  - Video Group: 1976-2003 [RESTRICTED], 196525 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Video Group: 1985-, 196524 (Offsite-box 497, Folder 2)
  - Video Group: 1977: Strategic Directions Conference: TV & Film Time Inc., 196523 (Offsite-box 497, Folder 3)
  - Wallpaper*, 196522 (Offsite-box 497, Folder 4)
  - Warner Books, 196521 (Offsite-box 497, Folder 5)
  - Warner Bros.: Consumer Products, 196520 (Offsite-box 497, Folder 6)
  - Warner Bros.: International Theatres, 196519 (Offsite-box 497, Folder 7)
  - Warner Bros.: Television/Lorimar, 196518 (Offsite-box 497, Folder 8)
  - Warner Bros. Television: WB Network: 2000-, 196517 (Offsite-box 497, Folder 9)
  - Warner Bros.: WEA Inc., 196516 (Offsite-box 497, Folder 9)
  - Warner Communications: 1989-1990, 196515 (Offsite-box 497, Folder 11)
  - Warner Communications: 1991-, 196514 (Offsite-box 497, Folder 12-14)
  - Warner Home Video, 196513 (Offsite-box 497, Folder 15)
  - Warner Music Group: Ice-T Controversy, 196512 (Offsite-box 497, Folder 16)
  - Whittle Communications: Channel 1, 196511 (Offsite-box 497, Folder 17)
  - Warner Music Group: Miscellaneous, 196510 (Offsite-box 497, Folder 18-19)
  - Washington Star, 196509 (Offsite-box 497)
  - Washington Star [RESTRICTED], 196508 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Whittle Communications: Miscellaneous, 196507 (Offsite-box 497, Folder 22)
  - Working Woman, 196506 (Offsite-box 497, Folder 23)
  - Working Woman: in Japan, 196505 (Offsite-box 497, Folder 24)